solidworks.com.cn 2003-12-02

# SolidWorks Privacy Policy

SolidWorks Corporation would like to thank you for visiting our website. We know many visitors have questions regarding the privacy of their interactions on our website. We hope this privacy policy statement will answer any questions you may have, but if it does not, please feel free to contact us at the email address or postal address shown below. 

Visiting our Website ****  
In general, you can visit the SolidWorks website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself, such as your name, phone number, or postal or email address. Our web server collects IP addresses to obtain certain aggregate information concerning the use of our website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. Therefore you can remain anonymous when you visit our website. 

Our web servers also collect information such as number of visits, average time spent on the site, and pages viewed, but this information is not traceable back to an individual user. SolidWorks uses this information to analyze how people use our site and generate ideas on how the site might be improved. 

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" so that we can better serve you with tailored information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers that a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. It may do such things as store the fact that you have registered for a seminar so that the next time you visit the site we recognize you are a registrant. You can, if you wish, set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some areas of some sites may not function properly. 

Occasionally you may be asked to give us more specific information about yourself, such as when you download software, register for a seminar or other event, respond to a survey or enter a contest from our website. Supplying such information to us is optional, but you may be unable to complete certain transactions without giving such information. 

The Use of Personal Information ****  
SolidWorks may use the personal information you provide us for a variety of purposes, including registration, authentication, and marketing purposes. We may use the information to inform you of special offers, upgrades and other SolidWorks products and services that may be of interest to you. Personal information may be shared so that you may receive a subscription to a SolidWorks user magazine from the publisher of the magazine. We may also share your information so that SolidWorks partners or other companies and organizations whose products we think may be of interest to you may contact you without obtaining your personal information. Furthermore, if you inform SolidWorks that you wish to be contacted by a SolidWorks reseller, we will forward information that you submit to SolidWorks to the reseller. 

You may use the SolidWorks web site to email your resume to SolidWorks. SolidWorks will keep your resume strictly confidential and use it only in the context of filling employment opportunities at SolidWorks. 

SolidWorks products are not marketed to children under the age of 13 years old and SolidWorks does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 years old. SolidWorks is committed to protecting the privacy of children and if SolidWorks becomes aware that such information was collected, will treat that information as sensitive. 

If you do not want information you provide to be shared, or if you do not wish to receive information about additional SolidWorks products or services or those of its partners and other companies, please let us know (see the contact information below) and we will respect your wishes. 

SolidWorks stores the personal data of customers and web site visitors indefinitely and may maintain and process such information directly or indirectly in one or more databases. If you provide personal information to SolidWorks, you agree and consent to SolidWorks' storage and usage of this information anywhere that SolidWorks and its affiliates maintain offices for the purposes described above. SolidWorks takes reasonable precautions to protect the personal data from loss, unauthorized access, alteration, misuse, and disclosure. 

SolidWorks may also disclose such personal information if required by law or if SolidWorks believes in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process or protect the rights, property or personal safety of SolidWorks, our customers or the public. 

The SolidWorks website may contain information about third parties and/or links to other websites. SolidWorks is not responsible for the accuracy of such information and for the privacy practices, security, or more generally, the content of these websites. 

****Updating Personal Information and "Opting Out"  
SolidWorks wants to ensure that the information it collects is accurate. Please notify us of any change to your address, phone number, email address or other information by sending us an email message at [privacy@solidworks.com ](mailto:privacy@solidworks.com) or by notifying us in writing at 

> SolidWorks Corporation   
>  300 Baker Avenue   
>  Concord, MA 01742   
>  Attn: Legal Department   
> 

If at any time you wish to "opt out" of receiving information from SolidWorks, please notify us by sending us an email or written message at the addresses shown above. Please note that due to lead times on certain mailings and other contacts, you may continue to receive contacts for a period following your "opt out" notification. 

****Changes to this Policy  
SolidWorks may change this policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to review our privacy policy from time to time. 

See also Terms of Use.   

This Privacy Policy Statement was last updated in April 2003.
